Jagdish Mehra Collection
University of Houston Libraries
- Oral Recording
  - Banquet (continued), Tape 12 (Box 141, Item 12)
  - Schwinger's Talk (continued) and Abdus Salam, Tape 13 (Box 141, Item 13)
  - Gell-Mann, Tape 1 (Box 141, Item 14)
  - Gell-Mann, Tape 2 (Box 141, Item 15)
  - Gell-Mann, Tape 3 (Box 141, Item 16)
  - Gell-Mann, Tape 4 (Box 141, Item 17)
  - Gell-Mann, Tape 5 (Box 141, Item 18)
  - Gell-Mann, Tape 6 (Box 141, Item 19)
  - Clarice Schwinger, Tape 1 (Box 141, Item 20)
  - Clarice Schwinger, Tape 2 (Box 141, Item 21)
  - J. Schwinger, Tape 6 (Box 141, Item 22)
  - J. Schwinger, Tape 7 (Box 141, Item 23)
  - J. Schwinger, Tape 8 (Box 141, Item 24)
  - J. Schwinger, Tape 9 (Box 141, Item 25)
  - J. Schwinger, Tape 14 (Box 141, Item 26)
  - J. Schwinger, Tape 15 (Box 141, Item 27)
  - Abdus Salam, Tape 1, April 11, 1989 (Box 141, Item 28)
  - Abdus Salam, Tape 2, April 20, 1989 (Box 141, Item 29)
  - Abdus Salam, Tape 3, April 26, 1989 (Box 141, Item 30)
  - Abdus Salam, Tape 4, April 28, 1989 (Box 141, Item 31)
  - Abdus Salam, Tape 5, April 29, 1989 (Box 141, Item 32)
  - Abdus Salam, Tape 6, April 30, 1989 (Box 141, Item 33)
  - Abdus Salam, Tape 7, April 30, 1989 (Box 141, Item 34)
  - Abdus Salam, Tape 8, May 1, 1989 (Box 141, Item 35)
  - Visionary Experience (Box 142, Item 1)
  - Timeless Moment (Box 142, Item 2)
  - Man on Earth - Or the Moon - Aldous Huxley and Charter, Tape 1, August 1962 (Box 142, Item 3)
  - The Chicago Centennial - Aldous Huxley, Tape 1 (Box 142, Item 4)
  - Visionary Experience - Aldous Huxley, Tape 1 (Box 142, Item 5)
  - The Ultimate Revolution - Aldous Huxley, Tape 1 (Box 142, Item 6)
  - Man in a Brave New World - Aldous Huxley, Tape 1 (Box 142, Item 7)
  - This Timeless Moment, Tape 1 (Box 142, Item 8)
  - Man in a Brave New World, Tape 1 (Box 142, Item 9)
  - What a Piece of Work is Man I - Huxley, Tape 1 (Box 142, Item 10)
  - What a Piece of Work is Man II - Huxley, Tape 1 (Box 142, Item 11)
  - What a Piece of Work is Man III - Huxley, Tape 1 (Box 142, Item 12)
  - What a Piece of Work is Man IV - Huxley, Tape 1 (Box 142, Item 13)
  - What a Piece of Work is Man V - Huxley, Tape 1 (Box 142, Item 14)
  - What a Piece of Work is Man VI - Huxley, Tape 1 (Box 142, Item 15)
  - What a Piece of Work is Man VII - Huxley, Tape 1 (Box 142, Item 16)
  - Earth or Moon (Box 142, Item 17)
  - Ultimate Revolution (Box 142, Item 18)
  - Human Potentialities (Box 142, Item 19)
  - c-70 Chicago (Box 142, Item 20)
  - What a Piece of Work is Man, Tape 1 (Box 142, Item 21)
  - What a Piece of Work is Man, Tape 2 (Box 142, Item 22)
  - What a Piece of Work is Man, Tape 3 (Box 142, Item 23)
  - What a Piece of Work is Man, Tape 4 (Box 142, Item 24)
  - What a Piece of Work is Man, Tape 5 (Box 142, Item 25)
  - What a Piece of Work is Man, Tape 6 (Box 142, Item 26)
  - What a Piece of Work is Man, Tape 7 (Box 142, Item 27)
  - S. Wolfram, August 30, 1990 (Box 142, Item 28)
  - Ted Schultze, June 30, 1990 (Box 142, Item 29)
  - Speech by Dr. Radhakishanan, August 14, 1947 (Box 142, Item 30)
  - E. Fredkin and F. Crick (Box 142, Item 31)
  - E. Huggins (Box 142, Item 32)
  - Shuddha Brahma (Box 142, Item 33)
  - Willis Lamb, Tape 1, March 27, 1988 (Box 142, Item 34)
  - R.F. Christy, Tape 2, March 24, 1988 (Box 142, Item 35)
  - R.W. Hellwarth, Tape 3, November 11, 1988 (Box 142, Item 36)
  - Sheldon Glashow (Box 142, Item 37)
  - Willis Lamb, Tape 14, March 27, 1988 (Box 143)
  - Willis Lamb, Tape 13, March 27, 1988 (Box 143)
  - Willis Lamb, Tape 12, March 27, 1988 (Box 143)
  - Sheldon Glashow, March 30, 1988 (Box 143)
  - E. Huggins (Box 143)
  - Morrison Fredkin (Box 143)
  - E. Fredkin and F. Crick (Box 143)
  - Dr. Mehra (Box 143)
  - Matthew Sands, August 13, 1990 (Box 143)
  - Colloque Jauch (Box 143)
  - Lloyd Motz, November 25, 1988 (Box 143)
  - Geoffrey Fox, November 1988 and Elmer Heller, November 23, 1988 (Box 143)
  - Felix Bloch (Box 143)
  - S. Wolfram, August 30, 1990 (Box 143)
  - Walker and Barrish, August 29, 1990 (Box 143)
  - S. Berman, September 2, 1990 (Box 143)
  - John Hopfield, September 5, 1990 (Box 143)
  - H. Gast, September 6, 1990 (Box 143)
  - R. Hellwarth, August 31, 1990 (Box 143)
  - J. Zorthian, August 30, 1990 (Box 143)
  - Sirlin - Zorthian, August 27-28, 1990 (Box 143)
  - Unidentified (Box 143)
  - Human Potentialities - Aldous Huxley (Box 143)
  - Lloyd Motz, November 25, 1988 (Box 143)
  - R. Walker and B. Barrish, August, 29, 1990 (Box 143)
  - A. Sirlin and J. Zorthian, August 28, 1990 (Box 143)
  - Carl Iddings, August 23, 1990 (Box 143)
  - Charles Bennett - IBM, July 29, 1990 (Box 143)
  - Corben and Leighton, March 20-22, 1988 (Box 143)
  - P. Morrison and E. Fredkin (Box 143)
  - H. Gast (Box 143)
  - John Hopfield (Box 143)
  - J. Wheeler, September 18, 1990 (Box 143)
  - J. Zorthian, August 30, 1990 (Box 143)
  - Landauer and Schultz, June 28, 1990 (Box 143)
  - R. Hellwarth, August 31, 1990 (Box 143)
  - Phil Platzman, June 25, 1990 (Box 143)
  - Meselson and Edger, September 14-15, 1990 (Box 143)
  - KUHF Mehra Interviews (Box 143)
  - Jagdish Mehra Artifacts (Box 144, Item 1)
  - Architectural Drawings of the Mehra Collection (Box 145, Item 1)
  - Dr. Mehra's Gap and Gown (Box 146, Item 1)